<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Gray Hat Freelancing</title>
    <link>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Gray Hat Freelancing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>2022</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static # Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating a github repository after cloning</title>
      <link>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Updating Github Repos # Yeah, I agree. Once they removed the easy ability to push updates to a repository after cloning (over http(s)). It&amp;rsquo;s been a nuisance to create your own or fork another, clone it, update the remotes for SSH and then get back to business. This reference is just a quick 1, 2, 3&amp;hellip; to-do/check list of steps for ease of reference!
Create repository on Github - Go to the website and just create one using their form, get the empty skeleton Clone repository - git clone &amp;lt;your repo&amp;gt; Remove remotes - git remote remove origin Add SSH remotes - git remote add origin git@github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TryHackMe - Olympus Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/tryhackme_walkthrough_olympus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/tryhackme_walkthrough_olympus/</guid>
      <description>Task 1 | Connection # https://tryhackme.com/room/olympusroom is a medium difficulty room on [https://tryhackme.com/](TryHackMe training platform) by Gavroche.
It&amp;rsquo;s primary focus is sql injection, in my opinion, with a slant on enumeration and systems comprehension.
We&amp;rsquo;re going to get started by adding olympus.thm to our /etc/hosts file to assist with enumeration.. this is recommended in the description and I&amp;rsquo;ve adopted it as a solid sign that we&amp;rsquo;ll need to do subdomain enumeration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.grayhatfreelancing.com/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo # Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs # Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
